lifesitenews.com 2007-06-16

# LifeSite - Your Life, Family and Culture Outpost

| 

LifeSiteNews.com has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. 

LifeSite Daily News, a key service in the LifeSiteNews.com family, is an alternative to the mainstream news media. Every day we gather the most important news on life and family issues from Canada, the U.S. and around the world. We give you the truth that is usually not available from your local media. The registration process is used to tailor the news sent to your email address. See "Use of Registration Information" below. 

For information about LifeSiteNews.com's services, please see the following page: [ http://www.lifesite.net/aboutlifesite/](http://www.lifesite.net/aboutlifesite/). 

**Use of Registration Information**   
Our site's registration area requires customers to supply contact information, such as name and e-mail address, and demographic information, such as your mailing information, including province/state and country. 

**Geographic data** (country, province/state, city, postal code and area code) is used only to direct certain stories or political information to those who would live in the area where it applies. 

**Use of Order Information**   
When you place an order, LifeSiteNews.com requests information such as address and credit card number. 

Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products and services. 

**Security**   
LifeSiteNews.com features security measures to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information placed under our control. The site utilizes a Thawte SSL digital certificate for secure credit card transactions. 

**Children's Guidelines**   
We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information. 

**Subscribe/Unsusbscribe**   
LifeSiteNews.Com allows users to unsubscribe from receiving e-mail from us. To unsubscribe from the mailing list, please go to the unsubscribe page:   

**Correct/Update Personal Information**   
LifeSiteNews.Com allows you to change or modify your personal information by sending e-mail to remove an e-mail address or by visiting a designated customer service page. 

**Disclaimer**   
This site contains links to other sites. LifeSiteNews.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

**Contact Us**   
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us at [ http://www.lifesitenews.com/aboutlifesite/contact.html](http://www.lifesite.net/aboutlifesite/contact.html)

| 

### NewsBytes

Last Updated  
2007-06-15 02:34:25 ET

[After years of urging the public and governments to support the destruction of embryos, scientists may have led them up a blind alley ](http://www.mercatornet.com/articles/is_therapeutic_cloning_obsolete/)

[A palliative care physician remembers an unexpected request from the husband of a dying patient ](http://www.mercatornet.com/articles/cant_you_give_her_a_needle/)

[Kenya Human Rights Commission calls for legalization of abortion ](http://www.capitalfm.co.ke/news/newsarticle.asp?newsid=2354&newscategoryid=1)

[Infanticide, Abortion Responsible for 60 Million Girls Missing in Asia ](http://www.foxnews.com/story/0,2933,281722,00.html)

[A Resurgence of Active Opposition to Federal Judicial Nominations ](http://www.freecongress.org/commentaries/2007/070613.aspx)

[Ontario voters will get their chance to vote on a new electoral system but will they even understand what they're voting for? ](http://www.westernstandard.ca/website/index.cfm?page=article&article_id=2569)

[General Pace latest victim of homosexual agenda, says military monitor ](http://www.onenewsnow.com/2007/06/general_pace_latest_victim_of_.php)

[Southwest Airlines stands by sponsorship of DC 'homosexual pride' event ](http://www.onenewsnow.com/2007/06/southwest_airlines_stands_by_s.php)

[Teen Suicide: A Matter of "Sexual Orientation" or Sex Abuse? ](http://www.cwfa.org/articles/13178/BLI/dotcommentary/index.htm)

[Pro-Life Music Festival to Draw Thousands, Top Christian Artists ](http://www.christianpost.com/article/20070614/27956_Pro-Life_Music_Festival_to_Draw_Thousands,_Top_Christian_Artists.htm)

[Brownback Speaks on Faith in Politics, Calls for Defense of Marriage, Life ](http://www.ewtn.com/vnews/getstory.asp?number=79721)

[John Tory 'Quietly' Recruiting strong liberals to run as Ontario Progressive Conservative Party Candidates ](http://www.thestar.com/article/215598)

[Amnesty International is now part of evil it set out to oppose ](http://www.alive.ie/editorsjottings.php#editorsjottings2)

[Massachusetts Governor plans to march -- against gay marriage ban ](http://www.boston.com/news/globe/city_region/breaking_news/2007/06/governor_plans_1.html)
